Atena (Afagh) Razmpoush Junior Front-End Developer

Vancouver, BC | 236-777-0343 | atenarazm@gmail.com | LinkedIn

Personal Statement

As a junior Front-End Developer, my priority is improving customer's satisfaction, company's profit, and my technical skills' growth. From my business and hospitality experiences, I bring the ability to communicate with customers and collaborate with coworkers.

Skills

- Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL, Microsoft SQL Server
- Tools & Frameworks: Photoshop, Bootstrap, jQuery, React, Angular, VUE JS
- Speaking English, Persian and Armenian
- Business Skills: Team Leadership, Negotiation, Project Coordination

Work Experience

ZOOM Moderator | Freelancer | Jan 2021 - Present | Vancouver, Canada

 Addressed basic technical issues the participants faced, and provided first aid mental support in case participants had triggered or experienced panic attacks during the training

Fashion Associate | Plum & Caposhie Clothing Store | Mar 2019 - Feb 2020 | Vancouver, Canada

- Learned the core values of the company as well as the characteristics and fabrics of different products to confidently assist diverse customers and increase sales
- Investigated customers' needs, such as their style preferences and occasion for shopping, to offer the best matching selection in the store

Freelance Web Designer | Boulevard Dry Cleaners | Dec 2019 - Feb 2020 | Vancouver, Canada

- Assessed client needs, priorities and business goals which resulted in the decision to create a single page website using WordPress, Elementor plugin, and additional CSS customization
- Collaborated with a professional photographer to shoot on-location pictures that would deliver the brand image of "welcoming, professional customer service"
- Designed content and visual branding for the website to reflect the business's value of eco-friendly service

Atena (Afagh) Razmpoush

Junior Front-End Developer

Vancouver, BC | 236-777-0343 | atenarazm@gmail.com | LinkedIn

 Published the website (boulevarddrycleaners.com) on Bluehost and maintained the website by taking care of the plugin updates, content updates, hosting and domain renewal

Director of Public Relations and Advertising | Association of Calligraphers of Rash | Apr 2017 - Sep 2018 | Tehran, Iran

- Sold out daily classes through new marketing strategies such as print flyers, verbal marketing, social marketing on Instagram, and special promotions for early bird registrations
- Expanded public awareness of the association by partnering with exhibiting artists in the same arts & cultural complex to create mutual advertising opportunities
- Implemented processes to improve efficiency and quality of responses to client enquiries

Project Assistant | International Media Academy | 2015 - 2016 | Yerevan, Armenia

- Coordinated accommodation, catering service, conference hall, and technical equipment for the media trainings financed by German foreign ministry incorporation with German Embassy Yerevan
- Saved 15% of the allocated budget for a 2-week training for a group of 12 participants and 2 international trainers through negotiation

Staff Welfare Service Director | Goharfam Persian Mines Company | Jun 2011 - Aug 2012 | Tehran, Iran

- Coordinated staff trainings for health & safety and English communication skills
- Scheduled, planned, and organized the holiday and business trips of the staff on a regular basis

Education & Training

Associate Certificate of Applied Web Development

BCIT | Vancouver, Canada | Expected Graduation in Mar 2021

Master of International Economics

European University | Yerevan, Armenia | 2012 - 2014

Bachelor of Tourism & Hotel Management

Bonyad Applied-Science Education Center | Tehran, Iran | 2006 – 2011